me is the Fermi
paradox the that we
don't see intelligent life
in our galaxy I
was if you guys
have any on Yeah
I've a lot about
that That can't be
the reason because we
should see all the
AIs that have So
just to clear everyone's
the idea is well
it's sort of unclear
why that would happen
right So if the
reason there's a Fermi
paradox there are no
aliens because they get
taken out by their
own technology we should
be seeing paperclips coming
towards us from some
part of the and
apparently we don't We
don't see any structures
Dyson spheres nothing whether
they're AI or sort
of biological So to
me there has to
be a different answer
to the Fermi paradox
I have my own
theories about that but
it's out of scope
for the next minute
But you I just
feel like
My feeling is that
we're past the great
filter It was probably
multicellular life if I
would have to guess
It was incredibly hard
for biology to evolve
that So we're on
You there isn't a
comfort of what's going
to next I think
it's for us to
write as humanity what's
going to next